citypaper.net 2009-09-17

# Privacy Policy :: Philadelphia City Paper :: Philadelphia Arts, Restaurants, Music, Movies, Jobs, Classifieds, Blogs

PRIVACY POLICY

To help you understand how information submitted via survey, e-newsletter sign-up form and all other information that may be captured when using our website, citypaper.net offers this Privacy Policy. Use of citypaper.net website, and disclosure to us of your personal information is optional and voluntary. By visiting citypaper.net, you are accepting and agreeing to the practices described in this policy.

The following paragraphs describe the type of information citypaper.net collects, the reason why such information is collected, how such information is used and who has access to it.

Collection of Information:

Citypaper.net collects information in various ways that is volunteered by visitors to our site. Certain identifying information, such as name, street address, city, state, zip, age and email address is gathered at certain interactive areas on the site, such as when you fill out surveys, subscribe to our electronic newsletter and enter promotional contests.

Citypaper.net uses tracking information to determine popularity of certain sections of our site based traffic to those areas. This information is reported in the aggregate form. Specific user habits are not shared with anyone.

Visitors to citypaper.net have options about submitting certain information. Such choices include:

Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters.

Opting not to enter a promotional contest, which completely alleviates the need for collecting information from our users.

Surveys:

Occasionally, citypaper.net will administer survey's to better target our content to accommodate the interests, needs and opinions of our readers/users. Information from these surveys is collected and analyzed internally by citypaper.net in the form of aggregate data. Citypaper.net may disclose this aggregate demographic information to advertisers/third parties in reports that never display information about specific individuals.

Electronic Newsletter:

Citypaper.net uses the information you voluntarily submit for the mailing of our electronic newsletters (after you have voluntarily opted-in). Citypaper.net sends out electronic newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (weekly basis) and occasionally sends out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we're doing. Citypaper.net uses Stream Send for list management and reporting purposes. Stream Send along with other third parties are unable to access your account or any of your personally identifiable information. Stream Send's Privacy Policy is available online at http://www.streamsend.com/privacy.htm.

Promotions

Citypaper.net allows readers/users to log-in to our site and register to win prizes from third parties. Citypaper.net will occasionally send out notification emails to contest entrants about other promotions and events relating to their interests. Information collected from this registration process is used for internal purposes only (in the aggregate form) and never sold or rented to a third party.

Sharing of Information:

The information that you share about yourself when visiting citypaper.net, unless specifically stated in this Privacy Policy, is shared with citypaper.net.

If you do not want the data to be shared with citypaper.net, you may choose not to permit the data to be collected or transferred by submitting personally identifiable information on our site, or by using a particular service.

Internet Transmission

Unfortunately, no data transmission (whether an e-mail, survey response or other transmission) over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Information you send via the Internet could be viewed in transit by a third party. Citypaper.net assumes no responsibility and will incur no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during transmission. Once we receive your transmission, we will take reasonable steps to secure it on our systems. However, we cannot guarantee that this information will be absolutely safe from intrusion from others, such as hackers.

Children's Privacy

Citypaper.net is intended for individuals over the age of 16 and not for children. If you are under 16, please do not submit any personally identifiable information on our site. Children should always ask a parent or guardian for permission to send any personal information online to anyone.

Other Information About Your Privacy

Whenever you voluntarily disclose any information online in any forum, blog or comments section of our site, that information can be collected and used by others. In other words, if you post personal information about yourself please show discretion so you do not receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

Additional Information

If, for any reason, you believe that citypaper.net has adhered to its Privacy Policy, please send your concern, compliant or other message to webinfo@citypaper.net. Citypaper.net will try to respond to your concerns and, where appropriate, attempt to correct the problem.

By using this website, you adhere to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms stated above, please do not use our website. Moreover, your continued use of this website after we post changes to the Privacy Policy implies that you accept those changes.

You may contact us regarding specific questions about this Privacy Policy and experiences with citypaper.net by mail, email, fax or phone. Please contact us using one of the following:

Mail:

Philadelphia City Paper  
Attn: Online Administrator  
123 Chestnut Street, 3rd Floor  
Philadelphia, PA 19106

Email:

webinfo@citypaper.net

Phone:

215.735.8444

Fax:

215.735.8535
